Rin.
What kind of present do you want Santa to bring you?
I haven't decided yet.
You need to decide soon, or it'll be too late.
He has to come from far away, after all.
Is that so...
So, what is it that you want the most?
A lop ear.
Don't you already have one?
It needs more friends.
Good evening!
Sorry for being late.
No problem.
Rin-chan!
What's that?
A Christmas tree.
And this?
Just something work-related.
Can we set the tree up?
Sure.
Daikichi, hurry up!
Okay.
This one goes on the top, right?
That's right.
What's wrong?
Our place doesn't have a chimney.
Santa will find a way in. Don't worry.
I'll keep the door open, then.
You don't need to.
What's with the carrot?
It's for the reindeer.
Lights out.
Just a little longer.
Santa only comes to places where the kids are asleep.
Turn off the lights! Quick!
Yeah, yeah.
Dear Santa
Thank you for the present
Rin
I remember wanting to meet Santa, too.
Rin, let's eat.
Okay!
Thank you, Mr. Reindeer.